I mean where were you born.
I was born in the US.
Oh, cool.
Yeah, I'm going to be late to class.
Have a good day!
You too.
I hate when people say that.
My grandparents came from India.
I was born here.
I remember the 4th of July fireworks.
My dad lifting me onto his shoulders
so I can see better.
I'm proud of my heritage
but this is my home.
Once in a while someone thinks I don't fit
the definition of how an American should look.
They ask..
but where are you really from?
Because you can't be from here.
America isn't just one race.
We all come from different places.
I love telling my family story.
Why can't they ask about that
instead of making me feel like
I don't belong.