Well, I just thought. I...
I..I mean I was born in the US,
but my grandparents are from India,
if that's what you meant.
I'm so sorry I didn't mean to sound...
Can we start over?
Sure.
Do you want to join our bake sale?
I'd love to.
Perfect.
My grandparents came from India.
I was born here.
I remember the 4th of July fireworks.
My dad lifted me onto his shoulders,
so I can see better.
I'm proud of my heritage,
but this is my home.
Once in awhile someone thinks I don't fit
the definition of how an American should look.
They ask..
But where are you really from?
Because you can't be from here.
America isn't Just One race.
We all come from different places.
I love telling my family story.
Why can't they ask about that
instead of making me feel like..
I don't belong
So what's it for by the way
I'm trying to raise money for a dance.
Cool! When? Where?
Er..I don't think it's for you.
Trust me when I say you wouldn't like it.
Why? because I'm Indian?
What? No!
No. It's at the community center.
They're organizing a dance for the senior citizens.
I don't think it's for us just yet.
Not for like a long time anyway.
Yes, I get it.
Well, I will still bake for that.
Thank you so much!
I have to head to the class.
See you later?
See you around.