1
00:00:03,810 --> 00:00:04,370
Hi!

2
00:00:04,580 --> 00:00:05,770
Just heading out.

3
00:00:06,780 --> 00:00:07,970
Kind of a long day.

4
00:00:09,750 --> 00:00:13,230
I was..I was thinking about the conversation I had with Micheal earlier.

5
00:00:14,080 --> 00:00:16,760
I mean he was..he was really upset, right?

6
00:00:18,100 --> 00:00:18,680
I guess.

7
00:00:18,680 --> 00:00:25,930
I guess I just didn't realize that telling him he had an advantage will make him feel that all his efforts didn't matter.

8
00:00:26,520 --> 00:00:30,070
Coz' that's not what I meant. You know I ..

9
00:00:31,490 --> 00:00:32,970
I should really talk to him tomorrow.

10
00:00:34,950 --> 00:00:37,400
Anyway, I'll see you later.


