1
00:00:00,510 --> 00:00:02,670
Hey! Done for today?

2
00:00:03,690 --> 00:00:05,160
Cool. I'm just heading out.

3
00:00:05,610 --> 00:00:06,760
Did you sign up for the bake sale?

4
00:00:08,080 --> 00:00:11,220
That bake sale girl. I'm thinking about it all day.

5
00:00:11,820 --> 00:00:14,670
I hate when people ask me that. Where are you really from?

6
00:00:15,400 --> 00:00:18,120
Anyway, I gotta catch my bus. I'll see you tomorrow? 


