1
00:00:04,110 --> 00:00:05,210
Hey!

2
00:00:05,520 --> 00:00:06,290
Heading home?

3
00:00:08,600 --> 00:00:09,240
Cool.

4
00:00:09,840 --> 00:00:11,890
Listen, I just wanted to say thank you again.

5
00:00:13,140 --> 00:00:15,740
I think you made Rebecca think about what she was actually saying.

6
00:00:16,460 --> 00:00:17,890
Even if she didn't mean it that way.

7
00:00:18,610 --> 00:00:21,470
Sometimes just asking why makes people think.

8
00:00:21,950 --> 00:00:23,160
Anyway,

9
00:00:25,370 --> 00:00:25,920
I gotta go.

10
00:00:26,280 --> 00:00:27,160
See you tomorrow?