1
00:00:00,820 --> 00:00:02,250
It wasn't my intention at all.

2
00:00:02,560 --> 00:00:03,820
I know, but think about it.

3
00:00:04,800 --> 00:00:06,050
Hey! Heading out?

4
00:00:07,580 --> 00:00:08,490
Us too.

5
00:00:08,800 --> 00:00:11,760
I was just telling her about 
what happened earlier with Michael.

6
00:00:11,910 --> 00:00:17,820
I guess, I didn't really realized that by saying that he had an advantage 
made him feel like all of his efforts didn't matter.

7
00:00:17,820 --> 00:00:22,680
Just talk to him. I need to talk to Li too.
She seems a bit down after our meeting today.

8
00:00:22,680 --> 00:00:24,070
Yeah, I thought so too.

9
00:00:24,170 --> 00:00:27,440
Anyway, we should head out. We'll miss the bus.

10
00:00:27,980 --> 00:00:28,810
See you tomorrow.

11
00:00:28,820 --> 00:00:29,490
Bye!



