1
00:00:02,030 --> 00:00:03,760
Hey! Done for today?

2
00:00:04,080 --> 00:00:08,610
Un,I felt a little weird after today's study group. 
Li just storm off in the end.

3
00:00:10,300 --> 00:00:11,430
I don't know.

4
00:00:11,430 --> 00:00:16,030
I mean I just want to get the presentation over and with a good grade.

5
00:00:19,040 --> 00:00:20,260
You think so?

6
00:00:21,230 --> 00:00:23,050
Maybe we did ignore her a bit.

7
00:00:24,000 --> 00:00:25,380
I should probably talk to her.

8
00:00:25,880 --> 00:00:27,020
See you tomorrow?

9
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


10
00:00:00,000 --> 00:00:00,000


