I'll' check it and let you know.
Thank you!
You're welcome!
Hi!
Don't worry about it.
We're just geting started.
We don't have a lot of time
so let's cut to the chase.
What does that mean?
Uh, don't worry about it.
Let's start?
I summed up all the key points
for our presentation.
Here you go.
Wow, this is awesome.
Thank you for doing this.
No problem.
I figure it could help speed things up.
Let me know if you have any questions.
Um, where is the part that I wrote?
Did you receive my e-mail?
I did, and it was really good.
You did a great job,
but..it was just some of the phrasing.
I didn't really have time to rewrite it.
Don't worry,
we covered some of your points elsewhere.
Look we all refer to your research here.
What do you think?
Never mind. Let's move on.
Alright.
I was also thinking of a way
to share the presentation between us.
So you can do the introductions,
you can talk about the research and hypothesis.
Okay.
You can talk about the procedure,
and I'll present the results and conclusion.
Sound good with everyone?
Um, what's my role?
Um, the introductions.
It's pretty simple.
Can I say more?
Well. It's not that long
of a presentation.
Hmm. Hey what if you also introduce
the main topics.
I was hoping to do more than just introduce.
Including the topic intros,
I think it'll be fine.
and we can help you with the wording.