I will check it and let you know.
Thank you!
You are welcome!
Hi!
Don't worry about it.
We are just geting started.
We don't have a lot of time.
So let's cut to the chase.
What does that mean?
Ah. Don't worry about it.
Let's start.
I sumed up all the key points
for our presentation.
Whoa! This is awsome.
Thank you for doing this.
No problem.
I think it will help speed things up.
Let me know if you have questions.
Um. Where is the part that I wrote?
Did you receive my e-mail.
I did,and it was really good. You did a great job.
It was just some of the phrasing.
I didn't really have time to rewrite it.
Don't worry we covered some of your points else where.
But we all refer to your research here.
What do you think?
Never mind. Let's move on.
All right./nI'm also thinking of a way to share the presentation between us.
So you can do the introductions.
You can talk about the research and hypothesis.
OK
You can talk about the procedure,
and I will present the result and conclusion.
Sound good with everyone?
Um, what's my role?
Um, the introduction. It's pretty simple.
Can I say more?
Well. It's not that long of a presentation.
Um. Hey what about you also introduce the main topics.
I was hoping to do more than just introduce.
Including the topic intros. I think it will be fine,
and we can help you with the wordings.