I thought it'll be easier for you that way.
I think I can handle more. I want to.
Oh, okay. You know what,
I'll take another look at it.
Okay. Thanks.
Back home there was not a problem
that I could not handle.
Everybody used to say that I'm smart.
But here it is a daily struggle just to be heard.
I know my English is not so good,
but that doesn't mean that
my opinions and ideas matter less.
I wish they would just ask,
what do you mean, if they don't understand,
but they don't.
It's easier for them to ignore
to move on.
Without me.
I have so much to contribute.
If only they would make an effort to listen.
Hey.
Thanks for saying something.
Sometimes it is easier for me to just ignore it.
Thanks.