Okay, what if you start with the negatives
and then move into the positives?
Ah, sorry keep going.
Hey!
Maybe you can help.
I need to find three negatives and three positives
about myself for an interview.
You're not helping.
His master's interview is today.
He's like super nervous.
Okay. Keep going,
finish your answer.
I'm passionate about my work,
the program's goals fit my own,
and my background
offers a unique perspective.
That's perfect.
Yeah?
Yeah, that's perfect.
Okay, now,
finish your lunch.
We have other stuff to do today.
I think I have his
whole speech memorized right now.
You've been doing great
helping me rehearse.
This program is my number one choice.
Okay, relax. Alright?
You're a shoo-in.
I mean the interview
will go better if you relax.
Look, besides you have that extra advantage.
Why, because of my great looks?
Haha...
I mean you know universities
put emphasis on diverse candidates.
What do you mean?
I mean being different from the majority
of the other candidates
will boost your chances.
Look, listen. I mean you know I don't think that
gender or color should be a factor
but sometimes it is.
I mean it can hold you back
or it can push you forward,
so take advantage of it.
I would like to think they could
at least think about
an..and..and, and listen to what I have to say.
Well yeah, they will.
That, I mean that's not what I meant.
I don't know.
Can we just move on, please?
Okay. Come on, come on.
You...you know that's not what I meant.
Of course I think you can do it.
I just mean you can relax a little bit.
I mean, come on.
I mean come on, you know I'm just
trying to help, right?