OK. What if you start with the negatives
and then move into positives?
Ah, sorry keep going.
Hey!
Maybe you can help.
I need to find three negative and three positives
about myself for an interview.
You are not helping.
His master's interview is today.
He's like super nervous.
OK. Keep going.
Finish your answer.
I am passionat about my work.
The program's goals fit my own.
And my background
offers a unique perspective.
That's perfect.
Yes?
Yeah, that's perfect.
OK, now.
Finish your lunch.We have other stuffs to do today.
I think I have all his whole speech memorized right now.
You've been doing great helping me to rehearse.
This programe is my number one choice.
OK, relax. All right? You are shoe in.
I mean the interview will go better if you relax.
But besides you have that extra advantage.
Why?
Because my great looks?
Ha Ha.
I mean you know
universities put emphasis on diverse candidates.
What do you mean?
I mean being different from the majorities of the other candidats
will boost your chances.
Off course. I mean you know I don't think that
gender or color should be a factor.
but sometimes it is.
I mean it can hold you back or it can push you forward.
So take advantage of it.
I would like to think they could at least think about
and, and, and listen to what I have to say.
Well, yeah, they will.
I mean that't not what I meant.
I don't know.
Can we just move on, please?
OK. Come on. Come on.
You know that's not what I meant.
Of course I think you can do it.
I just mean you can relax a little bit.
I mean. Come on.
You know I am just trying to help, right?