I mean, I don't know.
It's like that's how it works, isn't it?
I mean. Aren't schools obligated
to prioritize diverse candidates?
Well, you're making it sound like
that I can show up and it is a done deal.
Like all my hard work that I put in doesn't matter.
I mean, I guess I never thought about it like that.
Can we move on please?
Look Michael,
I'm...I'm...I'm really sorry.
That...that's not how I meant it at all.
Just forget about it.
Okay?
Yeah, okay.
Sorry.
It's okay.
Eat your food. Come on, girl.
I didn't just magically get here because I am black.
I'm a straight A student.
Top of my class.
I know I belong here.
This is what I tell myself everyday,
that I'm just as good as anybody else.
that I earn my spot by working hard.
When someone says something like that.
It makes you question yourself.
Like, am I really good enough to be here?
Or did they have a open slot
they had to fill with someone like me.
I wonder why she thought saying that...
would help.
Thanks for trying.
I wouldn't say anything,
but she's actually a good friend.
Anyway.
Wish me luck?